{
    "subject": "Emilio_Estevez",
    "predicate": "actedIn",
    "object": "The_War_at_Home__film_",
    "human_readable": "Emilio Estevez acted in the film The War at Home.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9878320097923279,
            "question": "Is 'The War at Home' a film starring Emilio Estevez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9859843850135803,
            "question": "What role did Emilio Estevez play in 'The War at Home'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8985952138900757,
            "question": "Name a film that features Emilio Estevez."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8898264169692993,
            "question": "Besides 'The War at Home', what other films has Emilio Estevez been in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8483631610870361,
            "question": "Who acted in the film 'The War at Home'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8412367105484009,
            "question": "What film did Emilio Estevez act in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.825792133808136,
            "question": "Emilio Estevez is known for acting in which type of movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8007001280784607,
            "question": "What is the title of the film Emilio Estevez was in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7350365519523621,
            "question": "In which movie did Emilio Estevez star?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3825327455997467,
            "question": "What is the genre of the film 'The War at Home'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Emilio Estevez acted in the film The War at Home.",
            "html": "yago_4026_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which movie did Emilio Estevez star?",
            "html": "yago_4026_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of the film Emilio Estevez was in?",
            "html": "yago_4026_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Emilio Estevez is known for acting in which type of movies?",
            "html": "yago_4026_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4026_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4026_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4026_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4026_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4026_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4026_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4026_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4026_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4026_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4026_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents support that Emilio Estevez acted in the film \"The War at Home.\" Multiple sources mention his role as a young Vietnam veteran who has difficulty adjusting to civilian life and his family."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}